Now that we have the owner setup,
现在我们已经设置好了合约的拥有者
we can modify our withdrawal function
现在我们就可以来修改我们的 withdraw 函数
to make it so that only the owner can actually call this withdrawal function.
使得只有拥有者才有权调用这个 withdraw 函数
So at the top of the withdrawal function,
所在在 withdraw 函数的顶部
maybe we want to add a section,
或许我们想要添加一部分
maybe we want to say require message dot sender equals the owner,
也许可以这样，require msg.sender 等于 owner
a note about double equals versus equals,
关于双等号与等号这里说明一下
you can think of this single equals as a set parameter.
你可以把这个单等号视作一个设置参数
So when I say owner, is now set to message dot sender,
所以这里就是把 owner 设置为 msg.sender
double equals is how you check to see if these two variables are equivalent.
双等号则是用来检查这两个变量是否等价
So we're saying is message dot sender, the same as owner.
所以这里就是在问 msg.sender 和 owner 是否是一样的
So this is checking to see equivalence. This is setting
所以这个是检查是否等价，这个是设置
checking to see equivalence setting.
检查是否等价，设置
So we're gonna say require message dot sender is equal to owner,
所以我们写下的就是 require msg.sender 是否等于 owner
otherwise, we're gonna throw an error, saying, sender is not owner. Perfect.
不是的话，我们抛出一个错误，就说 "Sender is not owner!" 完美！
Now we have a quick way to make sure the withdrawal function is only called by the owner of this contract.
现在我们就有了一个快捷的方法来确保 withdraw 函数只能被这个合约的拥有者所调用
Now, let's say that there's a lot of functions that we have in this contract
现在我们假设这个合约有很多函数
that are going to be required to be the owner,
它们都要求只能由合约的拥有者来调用
maybe there's a lot of functions in this contract
或者也可能是这个合约有大量函数
that need a whole lot of different requires,
它们有着很多各不相同的要求
we don't want to have to copy paste this line to every single one of our functions.
我们肯定不想反复复制这一行到所有的函数中去
So what can we do?
所以我们该怎么办？
Well, this is where something called modifiers come in.
这个时候就需要用到修饰器(modifier)了
So for now, we're gonna go ahead and delete this line.
现在我们要删掉这一行
And below, we're going to create something called a modifier,
并且在下面，创建一个 modifier
our modifier is going to be a key word that we can add right in the function declaration.
modifier 是一个可以直接在函数声明中添加的关键字
To modify the function with that functionality,
从而修饰(modify)给函数某些功能
we're going to create a modifier and call it only owner.
我们要创建一个 modifier 并且称之为 onlyOwner
And we're going to paste that line that we just made in withdraw.
然后把我们刚刚在 withdraw 里写的那一行粘贴过来
And underneath that, we're going to put a little underscore,
在下面我们还要添加一个下划线
what I can do now is I can take this only owner modifier,
现在我就可以把这个叫 onlyOwner 的修饰器
and stick it in the function declaration of my withdrawal function.
插入到我的 withdraw 函数的函数声明中
So what's happening with this modifier
所以这个修饰器到底有什么用？
with only owner in this function declaration,
这个函数声明中的 onlyOwner
we're saying, hey, for this withdrawal function,
我们可以这么理解，嘿，你这个 withdraw 函数
before you read all this code inside of it,
在你读取所有内部代码之前，
look down at the only owner modifier and do whatever is in there first,
先看看这个修饰器 onlyOwner 并且优先运行这里的代码
and then do whatever's in the underscore,
然后再运行下划线里的东西
this underscore represents doing the rest of the code.
这里的下划线表示运行余下的代码
So now, when we go call the withdraw function,
此处指的就是调用这个 withdraw 函数
we actually do this require statement first, and then call the rest of the code.
实际上，我们就是先运行了这个 require 语句，然后调用余下的代码
If this require statement, we're below the underscore,
如果把这个 require 语句，放到下划线的下面
this would tell our function to go ahead and do all this code first. And then run the require.
这将告诉我们的函数，先运行这里的全部代码，然后再运行这个 require
Because again, we have this only only keyword,
因为我们在这里有一个 onlyOwner 关键字
we're saying, Great, we've got a function, it's withdraw its public, oh, only odor modifier.
我们会说，很好，我们获得了一个函数，它叫 withdraw，是 public 的，哦！onlyOwner 修饰器
Let's look at how that works.
快去看看它让我们做什么
Okay, it tells us how to do all the code of the original function first.
好吧，它告诉我们先运行原函数的所有代码
So let's go ahead and do that. Okay, now we're done.
所以我们继续并且运行完这些，好了，已经完成了
Now, what do we do? Okay, now we'll run the require,
现在我们要做什么？好吧，现在我们要运行这个 require
we want to go ahead and put the require here first.
不过我们还是想把这个 require 放到前面
So this is how modifiers work, and how we can use them to improve our functionality.
所以这就是修饰器(modifier)的工作机制，以及我们是如何用它来改进我们的函数的